Hello friends welcome my channel today I am going to
tell you that there is a statement of ICICI Bank,
you have this statement in your mail, you
can open a shop with it, so I am going to
tell you how to open it, so I have
explained step by step, if you have a problem
in opening it then you also don't have a problem, you will
not need to watch this video on professional basis, there is no problem in your video itself,
sir physical, if you have
any statement or credit of your bank or
in which state you are here, you
can open it in the mail in this way, so friends let's
start friends, do
not subscribe to my channel, subscribe to the channel,
I keep bringing such videos for you
friends, friends I
would like to tell you that you have to
download the app from Play Store, download the best app,
Grid Worker and only after that
you have to open the second file,
you also say the correct password, then this
comes, you understand friends, you
entered a wrong password, you do not get the link, so
you have to download it once and
what you have to do after that friends I will
tell you the format now, the enemy has to
enter it, so friends what is your name
First you must have a name, take your surname,
only your name, its four letter
word, you have to write it in the mail, it should not be in the computer,
friends if even a single letter is
in capital then your name will not open, so what you have to do is to
take any letter of your name, first four letter, that too has to be written in small,
so the setting in your keyboard is
such that the first letter of is becoming chapter, then you will have to make
it small, so it will
open like this, then take the first four letter
and you have to take the date and mantra, then
you have to take the date of birth,
you have to take the day on which you were born and
in which month you were born, and
friends I would like to tell you that it is
necessary to put zero in front of it, which I have written, and in the date,
you just have to enter both, then
your name will open, so something